<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tags on Trails</title>
    <link>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/tags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tags on Trails</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Granite Park and Bear Basin</title>
      <link>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/granite-park-and-bear-basin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/granite-park-and-bear-basin/</guid>
      <description>Five days mostly off-trail in the High Sierras. Starting from Pine Creek trailhead north-west of Bishop we ascended into Granite Park, crossed over to Royce Lakes, into Bear Basin, over to Vee Lake, back into Bear Basin and looped around Italy Pass. Excellent views and at times difficult but still manageable terrain.
   Looking up north-west from Pine Lake
    Upper Pine Lake
    Granite Park</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Garnet Peak</title>
      <link>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/garnet-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/garnet-peak/</guid>
      <description>Short sunset / moonrise hike to Garnet Peak near Mount Laguna. This can be a busy hike, but July 4th and the late time had us meet just a very few other hikers on the way. The drop off into the desert from Garnet Peak is spectacular and so were the views with beautiful evening light.
   On the slope of Garnet Peak looking north
    Looking south</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvey Moore Trail / East Mesa Loop</title>
      <link>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/harvey-moore-trail-/-east-mesa-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/harvey-moore-trail-/-east-mesa-loop/</guid>
      <description>A beautiful hike through the eastern parts of Cuyamaca State Park. The trailhead is located at the Sweetwater parking lot along CA79.
A late start after 4pm resulted in hot temperatures during the ascent that gave way to beautiful mid-summer evening conditions and a seemingly never ending sunset. Some of the meadows were still in bloom. This hike does not climb any peaks but might just have the best views of all trails in the area.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lawson Peak</title>
      <link>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/lawson-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/lawson-peak/</guid>
      <description>The hike up towards Lawson Peak is alright, but once you get close to the top it gets really exciting. Climb your way up through cave-like openings between the boulders and you can make it all the way to the top. The views out towards the Pacific from here were fantastic.
   View from Lawson Peak towards the south-east
    View towards Mexico
    View towards the Pacific Ocean</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>South Lake to North Lake</title>
      <link>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/south-lake-to-north-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunnarvoet.github.io/trails/south-lake-to-north-lake/</guid>
      <description>South Lake to North Lake loop. Nothing less than breathtaking.
   Chocolate Peak
    Spearhead Lake &amp;amp; Long Lake
    Saddlerock Lake
    Saddlerock Lake after a cold night
    Bishop Lake with Mount Goode in the back
    Upper Dusy Basin
    Descent into LeConte Canyon from Dusy Basin</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
